i bought a dollar alien were lap
about stoller
well it is she they are definitely some photos to
it only came with a ninety one p
these supposed to have at least
we can do about that may be of spelling
anyway let's take a look and see exactly what we can do with such an old alone
is the import in extracting two thousand and eleven it definitely sports the old school aggressive eileen where desire nor any longer include a screen resolution as low as sixteen hundred by nine hundred and any of their laps
resolution was in fact
upgrade even back into thousand tenement looking at downside from the time we really takes you back second generation into couriers processes and a recommendation to use internet explore and nine
particular brick of lapps pretty expensive
configuration costing a stralian does it is now a little worse for whether the ceases the hinges kind of broken but i could just be the little cover of coming off hopefully and the rest of the laptop isn't all that dirty but some of the rubber is starting to become sticky and i doubt the single fan has ever been dusted out and we'll see just how bad it is later in the video
he was turning it on i used my big adele power adapted to supply the correct wattage then but into window seven not activated
the elasaid that the battery in this didn't work at all but when i plugged in the correct charging adapter the better i did begin to
although the health is only
so the battery one last long but at least it
which is
seems to be working for and he we can see it has a gigaboo ram which was an upgrade available back in truth thousand and eleven the mechanical hard drive in this computer
slow
i'm going to put in his
say that i raced
not only that we gain in towns ten
we can use the window seven license chats on the base of the
and with any luck we'll be able to act
while the drive isn't a very big capacity i can run games from an external aid and take advantage of the speed from the us b three ponomo laptop only had us boonapoort at the time but this chunky unit had
what can this well age to high specemine laporte in twenty
find
with windows ten successfully activated using the product on the base i tried out one of my favorite games ben and drive at the lowest graphical settings with a resolution of seven twenty p iteration france
abbut no ideal it was also getting hot with the spreading ninety eight degrees celsius
having a go at a competitive shoot accounts like go fer a little bit of running on manumitting at the native resolution
in average
i
totally pliable
a game that's rather taxing on old lapps is prayer unknown ballground
this battery or shooter ever just seventeen francs per second at the lowest graphic
and to be fair
to change the resolution no matter what so it may even run better at lower rise
so morgan differently struggle if they run at all at the native resolution of sixteen hundred by nine hundred halo combat of old in the master chief collection was only just playable averaging just twenty two frames
but how about much older games the two thousand and five release of stalwart battlefront ran very well at the highest rapacities averaging seventy nine point eight times
this kolosoff's great for games over ten years old after running a few games and benches on here i've come to the realization that is probably fertig
the end the invader
the single fan yes one fan for both
to an excellent requires
so i doubt anyone ever read on the family
or may be even claimed the
let's open it and see what we can
the ram battery had his cane optical drive is easy all the tanks is removing the truth
on the
this batteries health is below sixty per cent however you really can't run old gaming laptop off for the battery anyway the laptop must have been taken apart with some force
holding the optical drive cable in place had
not a big deal it can still be carefully pushed
another easy access pot is the ram you've got two lots that are populated by forgives
is still an adequate amount even the leanest a basic to
a gaming and next to the wife in models as if there is room for a celludine
every other alien went device i've worked on his given me access to the professor and graphic chip without the need to dig further of this model we really requires you to take out many screws and also the top casing this is necessary to get to the fan which we can assume has accumulated a lot of dust in the last eleven years there aren't many resources on lineations to dis
this model just remember that i'm likely glossing over certain steps for the sake of a
in this vile i only telling to the video i followed in the description but definitely take it with a grain of soul now the very tactile feeling keyboard can come out even eleven years ago only in workyard came with angling while they seemed pretty fancied you can definitely get similar performance for less money from other brands were they better build in some ways yes this particular machine is stood but self is from devitalizing robber in other words some of the soft plastic coating is starting to melt driver support overheating and design floors are also sadly common with many old alien way love tops oh and i found a few random screws floating inside the casing it appears as if they originally held the hard disking
and details like that broken clips and strops brews are teasin that someone was a very careful working on this leptopus it also seems as if no one is ever taken at a part this far and i can see why an it's quite a lot of work to do and here we get our first look at the sizable calling pipes that lead to a single fan i feel as if this would have worked a lot better dissipating hate with a separate fan for each
and a boy we've really got enough dust to insulate an entire house no wonder it was running hot and if you've got an old laptop like this considering out the farallones or will thank you another piece of the overheating pie may also be the potentially dried out there compound and dried out it is this stuff can't have been very effective a transferring hate away from the
a white ericson with us a propah and be showered them were based from the head sink as well using an old tooth brush scrubbed inside the vent to release any debris in the way it's always worth looking inside the fan itself as dark and bold up near the edges defiantly much plainer now and while i had to unearth it was effective at any hair and dust i could find you can tell this is where the fan sat right underneath the keyboard and over all its not visibly young up with food or that dirty however i'll go ever with some eucalyptus oil one slide i did notice was that the hinged a bit of play in other words it was slightly loose and easy fixed with a small dab of lock tight to the ends of the main
followed by an application of new fimarcon ound it's important to plough as these processes don't have an integrated heat spread a meaning complete coverage of the die is he
now the reassembly can begin i feel a lot more confident piecing it back together as i took note of the steps it took me to take a
lessing the processes in you and your big alien were lapps isn't this time
a fool is assembly is not what the average consumer ever wants to
but something i like doing is cleaning things and with the help of some utility soil the top casing is now looking a lot less grubby some areas were as easy to clean since the robber has started to melt so they are a little bit sticky sadly being a man black surface it'll probably look dirty again within a few minutes of touching it still a lot cleaner for the time being the screen is mostly undamaged a sad from some scrape where it has made repeated contact with the edge of the keyboard and on the screen hinges able to clip the loose cover back on and i held it in place with a dab of glue so let's if there are any improvements to the gaming experience with the freshly cleaned out cooling system
lansing edifies the buds pro wireless blue truth he bids the sound clarity is also an found them very comfortable to wear
cancellation and really long battery life and if you want to pick one lays up there's only in
and i haven't paid me for this but they did send them over in honestly this impiety goodbye never be using my airports
activity the first game were dropping into his play and none battlegrounds the alien were run so much cool adding game play with both to cebu and gown at least twenty degrees celsius a pretty good improve
a mentiri his pretty taxing on the sea but which after the repast ran nearly thirty degrees cooler before it was almost hitting one hundred degrees the boiling point of water and for games like mine craft in a totally fine experience on the alien were frequently reaching over one hundred francs per second when used alongside the performance in harding made
sure to join my serve reflects well it's crazy to think that his laptop is nearly twelve years old but its age really shows when it comes to graphical performance i personally go for something to a little bit newer if you plan on using it for gaming so there we have an eleven year old alien weapon cleaned up and working pretty well once a
the inclusion of an ass definitely made a big difference but the five fifty five graphic
no wagon after run more in games which is real shame because it's in a really nice chasse with a pretty capable quartiers
anyway thank you very much for watching for a hundred twenty dollars i think
again would have been better for me
caraway thank you very much for watching i'll see you